Okay, so now let's go ahead and add the environment inside our project.
From that, what I'm going to do is open up the Unity as it's stored and on the Unity
as it stores search for Flitted Grounds.
This is a free package on the Unity as it's stored as you can see.
You can just go ahead and click on this add to my assets, then click on Accept.
After that, you can click on this open in Unity.
And then click on Open Unity editor.
It will open up the Package Manager on the Package Manager, make sure to first of all download
this Flitted Grounds.
This is the size of this Package and then click on Import.
It will open up this window, click on Import again, and now in few seconds the project
will be imported.
Once it is imported, it will show this arrow right here, so we need to fix this arrow.
You just have to double click on it, and then whatever editor you have, it will open
the script in that editor.
For example, I'm using Visual Studio code right, so it's these three arrows which we
need to fix.
And you don't fix it right here.
After this main attribute, we need to add two things.
Actually, let's do it right here at the start.
Well, so the first will be Unity Engine, then dot, then the second will be posting,
and then dot, mean attribute, okay, you can do the same for the other one, so Unity Engine
dot, post processing dot, and then right here as well.
You can just copy paste it, then just simply save the script, get back right here, and
click on this, yes.
After that, we are good to go, so we're going to click on Flitted Grounds, then scene, and
let's open up this scene, a, all right, here we are, let's double click on this FPS controller
actually way.
This is the FPS controller, let me turn off the case mode, if you click on GameView.
As you can see, this is the GameView, of this whole thing, all right, so what I'm going
to do is I'm going to delete the FPS controller, because we don't need that.
Then after this, I'm going to scroll down to the bottom end to delete the canvas, then
the FPS display, I'm going to delete that as well.
I'm going to do an also delete the even system as well.
After that, we need to remove these red boxes, so if you select one of it, and copy
its name, then paste it right here in the URL, create the top, remove the end number from
it, for example, the number was for, and when you do that, it will show all of these
cubes.
I'm just going to select all of them, and I'm going to simply, right here, disable
it's mesh renderer, all right, and when you do that now, as you can see, we are no longer
able to see it, but the colliders are right there, so that the player doesn't get out
of the environment, okay, as you can see right there as well.
After this, what we're going to do is, we're going to select all of these things by pressing
control A, and then I'm going to create a empty parent for it.
When you do that, you can name this as environment, that's it now, inside the environment,
we have this whole environment.
All right, if you click on game, we don't have any camera or anything, but don't worry,
we will be adding the FPS controller, and then everything will work perfectly fine.